

#### **PROFILE**

A professional with 3 years of experience in Banking and financial services. My expertise lies in AML Compliance functions, KYC, Customer Due Diligence, Adverse Media Check (Part of Enhanced Due Diligence).

Want to work in a high-energy, team driven and continuous learning environment that provides opportunities to enhance and leverage my skills to contribute to the success of the organization and helps in personal and professional development as I pursue my career.

#### **Contact**:

+91-7004025913

# **EMAIL:**

vivsh.2416@gmail.com

#### **Hobbies**

- Listening to music,
- Reading books

# SHWETA KUMARI SHARMA AML/KYC ANALYST

# **EDUCATION**

PGDM (Finance & Marketing), Regional College of Management, Autonomous

2013-2015; 8.1 CGPA.

B.Sc. (Math's Hons), Jamshedpur Women's College, Kolhan University

2010 - 2013; 59%

12TH, CBSE, Science

2010; 61%

10TH, CBSE, Science

2008; 79.4%

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

1. PWC (On Third Party), KYC ANALYST

MAY 2022 – PRESENT, Bangalore (Remote)

- Working on Deutsche Project for AML KYC including onboarding, verification of client data, performing due diligence checks, reviewing KYC documentations, Risk Assessment, liaising with the business and advising on KYC requirements.
- Complete KYC on boarding for new and pre-existing customer (KYC Refresh). Working with clients and internal partners to obtain all necessary support documentation to ensure completion of KYC records for complex client types in complex regulatory environments.

# 2. INFOSYS BPM (On Third Party), SR. KYC ANALYST

**SEP 2021 – APR 2022, PUNE (Remote)** 

- Working on periodic review for ICS Card Customers including identification and verification of client data, performing due diligence, also responsible for reviewing transactions and other aspects of customer activity to detect any suspicious patterns, conduct investigations and rapidly escalate them to prevent possible fraud/money laundering attempts.
- Based on research conducted using different application and tools, provides risk rating to the client.

#### 3. INDUSIND BANK PVT LTD, ASSISTANT COMPLIANCE OFFICER

JUL 2017 - DEC 2017, MUMBAI

- Working on implementation and managing an effective legal compliance program by developing and reviewing company policies.
- Advising management on the company's compliance with laws and regulations through detailed reports by assessing company operations.
- Ensuring all employees are educated on the latest regulations and processes

# 4. ROYAL BANK OF SCOTLAND, AML ANALYST

APR 2015 – SEP 2016, CHENNAI

- Investigating and assessing alerts for with the purpose of preventing financial fraud, money laundering and terrorist financing.
- Responsible for efficient identification and monitoring of suspicious activities and transactions by screenings on customer.

# **SKILLS**

- Proficient in MS Word, MS Excel, Power point.
- Strong communication, organization, details oriented, problem solving and time management skills.
- Proactive, Positive approach, able to learn concepts and procedures quickly.
- Have ability to think new and better ways of doing things.
- Contribute the best for achieving team and organizational goals.